Guide to the Collège de la Sainte Famille Collection AD.MC.028
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Entrance to Tawfiq Mosque in Helwan. 24 x 17.9 cm, 1884; 9107; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref193)
  Doors/Entrances; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Mosques; Helwan, Egypt; Religious Sites
- Sulfur Spring in Helwan. 24 x 18.1 cm, 1884; 9108; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref194)
  Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Springs; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Public Baths; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait of students on 26 Sharif Street in Helwan at the entrance to the College de la Sainte Famille. 16.1 x 23.8 cm, 1941-1942; 9109; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref195)
  Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Group Portraits; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Uniforms; Buildings; Architecture
- Villa balconies on Latif Street in Helwan. 24 x 18 cm, 1984; 9140; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref196)
  Italian Writing; Architecture; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings
- Group portrait of students with a teacher at the top of a rock during a field trip to the desert. 23.9 x 18 cm, 1940; 9141; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref197)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Hats; Deserts; Boys; Students; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Statues of Buddha by the water in the Japanese Gardens in Helwan. 18 x 24.2 cm, 1983; 9142; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref198)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Parks; Ponds; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Outdoors; Statues/Sculptures; Water; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt
- Class portrait. 17.4 x 23.8 cm, 1959-1960; 9143; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref199)
  Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Teachers; Students; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Men; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair
- Group outdoor portrait of five teachers. 30.4 x 20.9 cm, 1936; 9144; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref200)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Fezes/Tarbouches; Hats; Facial Hair
- Street view of Helwan. 8.9 x 12.9 cm, May 1984; 9145; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref201)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Streets/Roads; Architecture; Buildings; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Street Lamps
- Front view of Orthodox Cemetery. 8.9 x 12.9 cm, Undated; 9275; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref202)
  Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Orthodox Christianity; Cemeteries; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing
- Japanese Garden in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; 9328; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref203)
  Men; Water; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Ponds; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing
- A priest and a boy standing in water in Suez. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; 9329; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref204)
  Water; Children; Men; Suez, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Boys; Facial Hair
- Group of students sitting on top of a bridge during field trip. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; 9330; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref205)
  Bridges; Architecture; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Railways; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Boys; Transportation
- Four teachers at a table with a microphone. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1965-1966; 9331; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref206)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Ceremonies; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Men; Women; Microphones; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of boys school football team., 1940; 9332; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref207)
  Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Group Portraits; Boys; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Football; Italian Writing
- A group of teachers and officials with trophies during school event. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1 December 1980; 9333; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref208)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Ceremonies; Officials; Men; Group Portraits; Women; Schools/Education; Awards
- Students at the Suez summerhouse. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; 9336; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref209)
  Hats; Suez, Egypt; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Boys; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Photographic Prints; Architecture
- A portrait of a man sitting with a cane. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1978; 9337; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref210)
  Canes/Walking Sticks; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Italian Writing; Turbans; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair
- Al-Aryan Christian monastery. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1984; 9338; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref211)
  Photographic Prints; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Monasteries/Convents; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Churches; Orthodox Christianity; Gelatin Silver Prints; Religious Sites
- A group portrait of schoolboys with a donkey. 9 x 11.9 cm, Undated; 9339; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref212)
  Uniforms; Hats; Group Portraits; Boys; Animals; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Donkeys; Schools/Education
- Farmers with a plow dragged by cows. 13.9 x 9 cm, Undated; 9340; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref213)
  Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Agriculture/Farms; Landscapes; Cattle/Cows; Animals; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing
- Portrait of boys with their teacher at the Japanese Gardens during a school trip. 9 x 14 cm, Undated; 9341; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref214)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Boys; Uniforms; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair; Men; Gardens; Parks; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Students fishing for crabs in Suez. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; 9342; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref215)
  Fish; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Group Portraits; Fishing; Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Swimming; Teachers; Suez, Egypt; Boys; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing
- General Mohammed Naguib, former President of Egypt handing out medals and trophies. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; 9343; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref216)
  Uniforms; Arabic Writing; Military/Soldiers; Helwan, Egypt; Microphones; Men; Weapons; English Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Medals/Insignia; Government; Political Leadership; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Officials; Ceremonies; Guns; Awards; Facial Hair
- An official shaking a student's hand at a ceremony. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1980; 9344; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref217)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Boys; Uniforms; Women; Men; Officials; Ceremonies; Schools/Education; Awards; Medals/Insignia
- Schoolboys drinking water from a drinking fountain. 13.9 x 9 cm, Circa 1950; 9345; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref218)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Fountains; Drinks/Beverages; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Children
- Boys swimming in Suez. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; 9346; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref219)
  Suez, Egypt; Swimming; Group Portraits; Boys; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Red Sea; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Seas
- Men and a woman sitting with a priest at a table. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; 9347; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref220)
  Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Microphones; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; English Writing; Hats; Priests/Clergymen; Women; Men; Facial Hair
- A school portrait of schoolboys with their teacher and two priests. 9 x 13.2 cm, 1959-1960; 9348; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref221)
  Italian Writing; Uniforms; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Boys; Men
- Students on a field trip with their teacher. 8.7 x 13.4 cm, Undated; 9349; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref222)
  Teachers; Deserts; Boys; Animals; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Shepherds; Sheep; Landscapes; Children; Students; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Mountains/Hills; Men
- A group of schoolboys with their teacher. 9 x 13.8 cm, 1978; 9350; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref223)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Boys; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Uniforms; Men
- Boys with their two teachers. 9 x 13.8 cm, 1965-1966; 9351; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref224)
  Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Schools/Education; Teachers; Group Portraits; Children; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Uniforms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Men
- Boys picking out crops during a field trip. 8.9 x 12.9 cm, Undated; 9352; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref225)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Students; Teachers; Uniforms; Boys; Agriculture/Farms; Group Portraits; Children; Schools/Education
- A portrait of an elderly man. 9 x 13.8 cm, 1983; 9353; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref226)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Turbans; Photographic Prints; Men; Hats; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Individual Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair
- The exterior of College de la Sainte Famille from Sherif street. 8.6 x 6 cm, Circa 1941-1942; 9354; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref227)
  Italian Writing; Schools/Education; Buildings; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- An empty classroom. 6.2 x 9 cm, 1950; 9355; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref228)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Furnishings; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Furnishings; Architecture
- The painted backdrop of the school theatre. 9 x 14 cm, 1910; 9356; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref229)
  Theater; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Painted Backdrops; Performance Plays; Schools/Education; Arabic Writing
- School teachers sitting at a table with a microphone. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1965-1966; 9357; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref230)
  Teachers; Women; Men; Microphones; Students; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Bags/Purses; Schools/Education; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair
- Teachers and staff behind desks. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, 1987; 9358; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref231)
  Group Portraits; English Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Religious Crosses; Telephones; Men; Women; Offices; Teachers; Awards
- A wax sculpture of Gamal Abdel Nasser at the Helwan Wax Museum. 12.7 x 17.8 cm, 1984; 9359; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref232)
  Arabic Writing; Nasser, Gamal Abdel; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Statues/Sculptures; Museums
- Students standing on the balconies of their school. 11.7 x 17.7 cm, 1987; 9360; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref233)
  Architecture; Schools/Education; Students; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Group Portraits; Children; Boys; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt
- Students standing in lines, saluting the Egyptian flag. 9.4 x 15.2 cm, 1987; 9361; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref234)
  Photographic Prints; Teachers; Boys; Girls; Architecture; Uniforms; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Flags; Students; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Men
- A school portrait with four teachers and two priests. 7.7 x 17.8 cm, 1969; 9362; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref235)
  Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Children; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Students; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Women; Men; Facial Hair
- A school portrait with three teachers and three priests. 11 x 15.1 cm, 1969; 9363; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref236)
  Group Portraits; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Women; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Schools/Education; Students; Italian Writing; Children; Men
- Boys celebrating their trophy with two teachers. 11.6 x 16.7 cm, 1962; 9364; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref237)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Teachers; Group Portraits; Sports; Men; Schools/Education; Awards
- School portrait of fourth graders with their four teachers and a priest. 13 x 17.9 cm, Undated; 9365; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref238)
  Group Portraits; Children; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Color Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Students; Facial Hair
- Class portrait of boys with their teachers and priests. 12.7 x 17.8 cm, 1980-1981; 9366; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref239)
  Men; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Women; Boys; Students; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Children; Teachers; Facial Hair
- Class portrait with four teachers and four priests. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Circa 1977; 9367; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref240)
  Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Students; Women; Men; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Facial Hair
- Girls standing beside their beds in a school dormitory 12.7 x 17.6 cm, 1949; 9368; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref241)
  Group Portraits; Furnishings; Children; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Girls; Schools/Education; Uniforms
- School portrait of boys with their teachers and priests. 16.9 x 23.9 cm, 1953-1954; 9369; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref242)
  Men; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Group Portraits; Boys; Schools/Education; Children; Students; Uniforms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- School portrait of boys with teachers and priests. 18 x 23.9 cm, 1951-1952; 9370; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref243)
  Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Students; Men; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Medals/Insignia; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of doctors and nurses at the Sanatorium Fouad I. 17.6 x 23.5 cm, 1929; 9371; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref244)
  Hats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Sanitariums/Sanatoriums; Doctors; Nurses; Men; Arabic Writing; Women; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Lab Coats; Children; Facial Hair
- School portrait of boys with school staff. 16.8 x 23.6 cm, 1957-1958; 9372; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref245)
  Students; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of boys with two teachers and one priest. 18 x 23.9 cm, 1957-1958; 9373; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref246)
  Students; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Uniforms; Group Portraits; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Children; Boys; Schools/Education; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair
- School portrait of boys with two teachers and four priests. 18 x 24 cm, 1953-1954; 9374; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref247)
  Children; Schools/Education; Uniforms; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Students; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of boys with two teachers and one priest. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, Undated; 9375; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref248)
  Women; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Priests/Clergymen; Schools/Education; Boys; Group Portraits; Students; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Men
- A man riding a camel and another holding it's reins. 16.3 x 23.9 cm, 1900; 9376; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref249)
  Camels; Animals; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Men; Architecture
- Group portrait of students with a teacher and a priest. 18 x 23.8 cm, 1958-1959; 9377; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref250)
  Students; Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Teachers; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of students with teachers and priests. 14.5 x 19.2 cm, 1960-1961; 9378; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref251)
  Men; Group Portraits; Boys; Priests/Clergymen; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Students; Photographic Prints; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Teachers; Facial Hair
- Street view of ex "Hotel Antonio". 18 x 24.1 cm, 1984; 9379; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref252)
  Buildings; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Italian Writing; Men; Women; Streets/Roads; Hotels; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School portrait of boys with five priests. 17.4 x 23.1 cm, 1947-1948; 9380; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref253)
  Boys; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Schools/Education; Children; Students; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Facial Hair; Men
- School portrait of boys with eight priests. 18 x 24 cm, 1953-1954; 9381; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref254)
  Children; Students; Uniforms; Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Facial Hair; Men
- Street view of the Sainte Famille school. 16.8 x 23.8 cm, Circa 1950; 9382; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref255)
  Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Architecture
- Class portrait of boys with a teacher and a priest. 18 x 24 cm, 1955-1956; 9383; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref256)
  Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Teachers; Schools/Education; Boys; Children; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Students; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Men
- Girls from the Sainte Famille School parading with flags. 16.1 x 24 cm, Undated; 9384; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref257)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Streets/Roads; Children; Parades/Processions; Flags; Italian Writing; Uniforms; Girls; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Events/Occasions
- A group of workers cutting stone at a quarry. 12.7 x 17.7 cm, 1900; 9385; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref258)
  Mokattam, Cairo, Egypt; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Quarry/Mine; Workers; Arabic Writing; Construction; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Mountains/Hills
- School portrait of boys with six priests. 17.5 x 22.2 cm, Undated; 9386; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref259)
  Helwan, Egypt; Students; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Men
- Street view of Tewfik Palace. 17 x 24.2 cm, 1983; 9387; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref260)
  Cars/Trucks; Buildings; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Italian Writing; Streets/Roads; Arabic Writing; Hotels; Palaces; Transportation
- Group portrait of students with three teachers. 17.9 x 23.8 cm, 1958-1959; 9388; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref261)
  Uniforms; Men; Teachers; Group Portraits; Boys; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- Group portrait of students with three teachers. 17.7 x 23.6 cm, 1959-1960; 9389; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref262)
  Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Students; Teachers; Children; Men; Schools/Education; Boys; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait of ten Scout leaders. 12.9 x 19.2 cm, December 1977; 9390; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref263)
  Scouts; Uniforms; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints